Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
（佳乃(よしの)）あっ…
（野崎(のざき)・みか）あっ…
（斉藤(さいとう)）うん？
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
is for me to decide.
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
is for me to decide.
So there you have it.
Gantz! What alien is it this time?
（計(けい)）ガンツ 今度は何星人だ？
さあ 見せてみろ！
Come on! Show me!
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
is for me to decide.
So there you have it.
Please go eliminate
this target now,
No matter what you bring on,
I'll fuckin' kill it!
Please go eliminate
this target now,
you bastards.
No matter what you bring on,
I'll fuckin' kill it!
（計）何星人だ！
...now, you bastards.
No matter what you bring on,
I'll fuckin' kill it!
...now, you bastards.
Kurono Alien
No matter what you bring on,
I'll fuckin' kill it!
...now, you bastards.
Kurono Alien
はぁ？ マジかよ？
No way!
お… 俺？
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Put on the suits!
（計）スーツを着てくれ
Just put them on!
（計）とにかく着てくれ
The transfer will start soon,
and then the battle will begin!
もうすぐ転送が始まって戦いになる
We're going to fight YOU?
（野崎）お前と戦うのか？
（計）違う！
No!
Gantz is trying to set me up!
（計）これはガンツのワナだ！
絶対 そうに決まってる
I know it! It has to be!
I'm a normal, living human!
俺は普通の生きた人間だ
Hurry up and put them on!
（計）いいから 早く着ろ！
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Stop fucking around, Gantz!
（計）ふざけんな ガンツ！
（斉藤）ガンツ？ それ 何ですか？
Stop fucking around, Gantz!
Gantz? What's that?
こいつだ！ こいつがガンツだ
This thing! THIS is Gantz!
It's all his fault!
全部 こいつが悪いんだよ！
Kurono Alien!
Is this lucky or what?
（室戸(むろと)）これ ラッキーだぜ
（梶浦(かじうら)）ああ？
Huh?
We already died once, right?
（室戸）俺ら１回 死んでんじゃん
Those guys who shot us think so, too.
（室戸）
俺ら撃った あいつらだって
そう思ってる
If we make it back, it'll be like pushing
the reset button on our lives.
（室戸）こっから帰ればさ
人生 リセットできちゃうってこと
Am I wrong?
違う？
Plus,
しかもさ 帰る前に あいつら
皆殺しにしたっていいわけじゃん
we can kill all the others
before we go back.
First that thing opens up,
we can kill all the others
before we go back.
Then the weapons and suits come out of it!
We can kill all the others
before we go back.
Then the weapons and suits come out of it!
I mean, it's not a crime to kill people
who're already DEAD, right?
死人 殺したって
罪にはなんないでしょう？
There's a time delay with the guns,
I mean, it's not a crime to kill people
who're already DEAD, right?
And the suits raise your chances of survival!
All six of them. Six...
（室戸）６人だぜ ６人
Well, seven, actually.
（室戸）ホントは７人だけどな
You son of a bitch.
（室戸）てめえ 汚ねえ仕事は
全部 俺に やらせやがって…
You've been making me do all the dirty work.
This is just the right opportunity.
いいチャンスだぜ
（梶浦）
フン！ この殺人オタクが…
You murdering freak.
少年法で守られてるから
てめえを利用してるだけなんだよ
I'm just using you because you're
protected by juvenile law.
Who do you think you are spouting off
ideas to like that, you little shit?
偉そうに
アイデア出してんじゃねえよ
このクソガキが！
All right. We'll play the part a little longer.
ハハッ…
よし もうちょい芝居しとけや
Convincing them looks like
it could work to our advantage.
ヤツらの頭 取っといたほうが
何かと便利そうだからな
We'll get to do plenty of killing later, after all.
殺人ショーは
いつでも楽しめるからよ
Oh, I'm confident in my ability to ACT...
俺 芝居 自信あるんだ
So let me get this straight.
つまり こうですね　私たちが
生きて元の世界に帰るためには―
If we want to go make it back alive,
we have to fight you, right?
君と戦わなければならないと
No, that's not it!
違うんだって！ 今まで
こんなことは なかったんだ！
Nothing like this has ever happened before!
But that IS you in the picture, right?
（野崎）あの写真 お前(めえ)だよな？
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
（計）だから これはガンツが！
Kurono, what is Gantz?
（みか）
玄野(くろの)君 ガンツって何なの？
えっ？ あの黒い玉だよ
That black ball.
Now wait just a minute!
（古田(ふるた)）待ちなさい ちょっと
彼は未成年だぞ
This is a minor we're talking about!
We adults are supposed to
gang up on him and kill him?!
大人の私らが 寄ってたかって
彼を殺す？ そんなバカな…
That's absurd!
Would you do it if he was an adult?
（野崎）
相手が大人だったら やるかい？
（古田）フン！ バカなことを…
Don't be ridiculous!
Where have you been?
どこに行ってた？
（梶浦）トイレですよ
Bathroom.
Anyway, has anything been decided yet?
…で
話し合いは まとまりましたか？
We've just been going in circles.
（野崎）堂々巡りだっつうの
Ah...
そうですか
じゃ こうしませんか？
Well, why don't we do this?
Let's ask Kurono to give us some kind of proof.
（梶浦）玄野君に
何か証明してもらうんですよ
えっ？ 証明？
（梶浦）ええ
Proof.
Yeah. Something that would make us
believe we can fully trust him.
玄野君を全面的に信じていいと
我々が思えるような証明です
何かありませんか？
Do you have anything that could do that?
I just showed you the
power of this suit, didn't I?
スーツの力を
さっき見せただろう？
トリックかもしれないでしょう？
But it might've been some kind of trick.
Anything will do.
何でもいいんですよ
納得がいくようなことなら何でもね
Anything at all, so long as it can convince us.
Kato!
か… 加藤！
Kurono? What's wrong?
（みか）玄野君 どうしたの？
What's the matter?
どうしたんだ？
（斉藤）何か います？
Is something there?
Didn't you see that just now?
今のが見えなかったのかよ？
（佳乃）えっ？
（殴る音）
（加藤）やめてくれ！ アアッ…
Stop it!
Kei!
計ちゃん…
Kato...
加藤…
岸本も 待ってる…
Kishimoto... is waiting, too.
Stop it!
やめろー！
（斉藤）な… 何するんですか？
（古田）玄野君 銃を下ろしなさい
What are you doing?!
Kurono! Put the gun down!
（計）やめろ ガンツ！
Stop it, Gantz!
てめえ なに見せてんだ？
加藤は死んだんだ！ ガンツ！
You son of a bitch! What the hell are
you showing me this for?!
Kato is dead! Gantz!
あっ… そんな… バカな…
No... It can't be!
あっ… 来ないで… 来ないでよ！
Don't come near me!
Stay away from me!
Who the fuck are you?
誰だ？ てめえ
What is this?!
何だよ？ これ
Hey!
（野崎）おい！
Stay back!
（佳乃）来ないで
（斉藤）こ… こんな所まで…
They followed me HERE?!
Stay back!
Hey, what's wrong with you people?
（古田）みんな どうしたんだ？
Huh? What's going on?
（梶浦）ああ？ 何なんだ？
（室戸）さあ？
Please! Get away from me!
Huh? What's going on?
Beats me.
（佳乃）あっち行って！
Please! Get away from me!
Kato...
（計）加藤 俺 撃てねえよ
Get away!
Kato...
I can't shoot...
撃てねえって
I can't shoot!
No, stay back!
来ないで…
Don't come near me, you murderer!
来ないでよ この人殺し！
Stop it!
やめろ！
（発射音）
Gantz!
ガンツ！ 許さねえ！
You're gonna pay for this...
You're gonna pay, you bastard!
許さねえぞ この野郎！
あっ タイムラグが …ない
There was no time lag!
What the hell are you doing?!
いきなり 何をするんだ！
Awesome...
すんげえ
（みか）い… 今の何？
What happened just now?
It was him! He did that!
こいつですよ！
こいつのしわざですって！
He IS the Kurono Alien!
やっぱり玄野星人なんですよ！
（計）違う！
No, I'm not! I saw my friend!
友達がいたんだ
ここで死んだ友達が襲われてたんだ
My friend who died here
was just being attacked!
Did any of you see that?
皆さん 見えましたか？
Like anyone here's going to believe you.
（野崎）誰が信じるかよ
ホントなんだって！
It's the truth!
Or maybe... you just wanted to
shoot us for the hell of it.
君 もしかして―
ただ我々を
撃ちたかっただけなんじゃないのか
No!
ち… 違う！ 違うって ホントに！
That's not true! I'm serious!
これ 何か変だ！
今回は銃のタイムラグがない
Something's wrong here!
There's no time-lag on the gun this time!
今までは…
（斉藤）もう たくさんだ！
Up till now, it...
That's enough!
Mr. Kajiura said he wanted PROOF, didn't he?!
梶浦さんは納得のいく証明をと
言ったでしょう？
But instead of giving us that proof,
you suddenly tried to shoot us!
しかし 君は証明どころか
いきなり撃ったんですよ
It's impossible to trust you!
信じろっていうほうがムリだ！
Wait a second!
ちょっと待ってください！
だからって―
You can't just jump to conclusions like that!
そんなに決めつけなくても…
（梶浦・室戸）フフッ…
Listen to what I have to say!
俺の話を聞いてくれ！
（梶浦）どうします？ 皆さん
What do you think, everyone?
His story just doesn't seem that believable.
どうも その… 彼の話は
あまり信用できないようですけどね
（計）ンンッ…
（梶浦）まあ あれです
For now, let's put aside such disturbing
thoughts as whether to kill or not to kill,
殺すとか殺さないとか
物騒なことは ともかく―
and think of what WE should do on our own.
我々だけで
どうするか考えたほうが―
いいんじゃないですかね？
（斉藤）そうですよ
I agree! I can't trust him!
私は彼を信用できない
（計）おい！
Hey!
もし 本当に
私らの命が懸かっているんなら―
If our lives really are on the line,
then we need to sit down and
carefully talk this through!
ここは慎重に話し合うべきだ！
I think we should trust him.
（みか）私は
彼を信じたいと思うんですけど…
Trust a guy who just shoots without warning?
いきなり発砲するヤツをか？
（みか）あっ…
Well, how about this?
では こうしましょう
We all saw for ourselves the power
these suits seem to hold.
あの服が すごい力を
持っているらしいというのは―
さっき
我々が この目で見たわけです
Why don't we all put them on, just in case?
万が一に備えて
一応 着替えておきませんか？
Furthermore, we'll keep him under
strict supervision from now on.
ただしですね
彼には今後 厳重な監視を
つけるということで どうです？
What do you think?
C'mon everyone, change quickly!
I'll keep watch on him.
皆さん 早く着替えてください
僕が こいつを見張っときますから
And don't forget to grab a gun!
（室戸）それから 銃を持って
やめろ
俺は あんたらを撃ったりしない
Stop it! I wouldn't shoot you guys!
How do we know that?
そ… そんなの分からない
You just fired a minute ago!
今 撃ったじゃないか
（計）てめえ…
You bastard!
じゃ 順番に どうぞ
玄関で着替えられそうですから
Okay, you guys take turns.
You can change in the foyer.
Um, I want to trust...
あの… 私は彼を… あっ…
Let's go get dressed.
着替えときましょう
女２人なら時間も節約できるし
It'll save time if the two women
get dressed together.
But you're his...
あなた 玄野君の…
（佳乃）ええ 担任よ
That's right. I'm his teacher.
But none of that will matter if I die for real.
でも ホントに死んじゃったら
教師も何もなくなるし
I don't intend to use it,
私は撃つつもりはないが
護身用に―
but it might not be a bad idea
to take one for protection.
持つだけは持っておいたほうが
いいんじゃないかな
Well, going by what he told us,
（梶浦）さて 彼の話によれば―
we're supposed to be transferred
somewhere next.
今度は我々は どこかに
送られるということですが…
Go Now
ウワッ…
（野崎）アア…
Hey, what are you doing?!
何するんだ？
（計）それは こっちのセリフ！
That's what I want to know!
What are you two up to?!
お前ら 何たくらんでんだ？
Private Room
Peep Show
（みか）ここ どこですか？
Where are we?
If I remember correctly,
this building is ten stories.
確か 10階建てだったかな
The first floor is a European style bar,
１階が洋風居酒屋で
あと ２階から上は全部 風俗です
and from the second floor up,
it's all adult entertainment.
You certainly know this place well, don't you?
（古田）やけに詳しいんだな
（斉藤）あっ… いえ…
アア… か… 梶浦さん
Mr. Kajiura!
ガキに銃を取られた
That little shit took my gun!
チッ…
何やってんだ？ しょうがねえな
What the hell were you doing?
Well, it's too late now.
Everyone! You're seeing this, aren't you?
皆さん あれ見えますよね？
（古田たち）うん？
Give us the gun, Kurono!
（古田）銃を渡せ 玄野君
私らは 君を
どうこうしようなんて思ってない！
We don't intend to do anything to you!
I have nothing else to say!
（計）もう俺に話すことはない
信じなければ
あんたらが死ぬだけなんだぞ
If you're not going to trust me,
you'll only end up dead yourselves!
Anyway, just put the gun down!
（古田）
とにかく 銃を下ろしてくれ
We can't very well talk to
one another like this, can we?
それじゃ 話し合いにも
何にもならないだろう？
This is no time for a negotiation!
（斉藤）
説得なんかしてる場合ですか？
Can't you see he has a gun?
彼の銃が見えないんですか？
If you get shot, your negotiations
won't matter for shit!
撃たれたら
説得もクソも なくなるぜ
I know that!
（古田）
分かってるよ　だけどね 私は―
I just don't want to see a kid
with a future getting into trouble!
将来のある若い子が
荒れていくのは見たくないんだよ
Is that so hard to understand?
世の中 そうじゃないだろう！
みんなで協力して
どうするかを決め…
We can help each other and
decide what we're going to do...
人殺しは あいつらなんだよ！
THEY are the murderers!
What?
I saw them!
（計）俺は見たんだ！
あいつら ホームレスを
金属バットで殴り殺してる
I saw them beat a homeless man
to death with metal baseball bats!
I'm not lying!
（計）ウソじゃない
この間 ぶっ壊れて
ニュースで やってた羅鼎院(らていいん)だ
I saw them do it by Ratenin, that temple
that was on the news the other day!
Ratenin?!
（佳乃）羅鼎院？
Do you know anything about that?
何か知ってるのか？
（佳乃）あっ いえ…
Um, not really...
They killed the homeless man inside the temple!
（計）あそこの境内で そいつら
ホームレスを殺したんだ！
（梶浦）ハッ…
ヤツの言うことを信じるんですか？
Are really going to believe what HE tells you?
There's no way we'd do anything like that.
そんなこと
するわけないじゃないですか
You son of a bitch! How long are
you going to keep up this act?
てめえ いつまで猫かぶってんだ？
I saw you!
俺は見たんだ
（明かりのつく音）
He is a liar.
Murderer.
Kick His Ass!
He is a liar.
He Shoots Guns!
He shoots people with guns.
He Betrays His Friends.
He is a liar.
He shoots people with guns.
He Betrays His Friends.
He's HORNY.
He shoots people with guns.
He shoots Guns.
He is a liar.
Kick His Ass.
He's a murderer.
He Shoots Guns.
What the...
（計）な… 何だ？
Please Kill The
Kurono Alien.
Stop it, Gantz!
（計）やめろ ガンツ！
ジャマすんじゃねえ！
Don't get in my way!
This is Gantz's trap!
これはガンツのワナだ！
I told you earlier! Don't let him fool you!
さっきも言ったろう？
惑わされるな！
There he is again.
（斉藤）ま… まただ
He's coming.
（斉藤）く… 来る…
What's wrong, Mr. Saito?
（みか）
斉藤さん どうかしましたか？
イ… イヤだ！
（古田）おい どうしたんだ？
No!
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Leave me alone, already!
もう勘弁してくれー！
Stop it! Stop shooting!
（古田）やめろ 撃つんじゃない！
C'mon, get a hold of yourself!
おい しっかりしろ　何が見えた？
ああ？ 何が見えたんだ？
What did you see just now?
Tell me what you saw!
Everyone, calm down!
ちょっと落ち着いてくれ！
Now start Killing each other
to your heart's content
Kato...
加藤 やべえよ
誰も信じてくれねえよ
I'm in trouble. Nobody believes me!
（梶浦）とにかく
玄野星人をやっつけることです
Anyway, killing the Kurono Alien
is our top priority.
そうすれば帰れるらしいですからね
It seems if we do that, we'll be able to go home.
星人って 彼は…
Alien? But he's...
He's going down.
下に降りてますよ
Hey, what are you doing?
あっ… 何をするんだ？
（梶浦）バケモノ退治ですよ
We're just getting rid of a monster!
He got away.
（室戸）逃げ込んだ ８階辺りだ
He's around the 8th floor.
Then let's go down to the 7th.
７階まで下りましょう
下の階に下りさえすれば
ヤツはビルの外に出られない
If we go below him,
he won't be able to get out of the building.
（明かりのつく音）
ウワッ…
Shit!
くそ… ガンツの野郎…
Gantz, you son of a bitch!
Okay, he's one floor above us right now.
（梶浦）さて
今 ヤツは この上の階にいます
There are seven of us against one of him.
彼は１人 対する我々は７人
If we charge him, we could
easily take him down.
突入すれば簡単に倒せます
Wait a minute! We all believed
his story at one point, didn't we?
（みか）待ってください！
彼の話を
一度は信じたじゃないですか
What are you talking about?! I saw it!
何を言っているんですか？
私は見たんだ
He turned into that bill collector...
彼が あの取り立て屋に変わって…
So was it Gantz or Kurono that
made you see the illusion?
（野崎）ガンツと玄野と
どっちが見せた幻覚だかな…
It was Kurono, of course!
（斉藤）あの子に
決まっているじゃないですか！
I just want to go back! Please let me go!
私は早く帰りたい
お願いだ 早く帰してくれ！
YOU were the one saying what
a relief it is to be here.
ここにいると癒やされるって
言ったのは あんただぜ
Everyone, relax!
みんな 落ち着いてくれ
There's no need for us to argue
amongst ourselves, right?
なにも私らが
いがみ合う必要はないだろう
And you two over there! Why did you shoot?!
あんたらも あんたらだ
なぜ撃った？
Because we want to survive.
生き残りたいからですよ
Mr. Furuta...
（梶浦）古田さん あなたは
生き残りたくないんですか？
Don't YOU want to survive?
You're talking about two different things!
（古田）それとこれとは別だ
You shouldn't be using that gun!
銃なんか撃っちゃいけない！
（みか）そうですよ
He's right! We still don't know
if he's our enemy or not!
彼が敵かどうか
まだ分からないじゃないですか
But we have no choice.
（佳乃）しかたないじゃないの
（みか）えっ？
（佳乃）生き残りたいのは
誰だって同じよ　だったら 彼を…
We all want to survive.
So that means we have to...
What other way is there?
ほかに方法があるの？
（みか）あっ…
But you're Kurono's...
あなたは玄野君の…
You're getting on my nerves!
さっきから うるさいわね
ええ 担任よ！ それが何なのよ？
Yes, I'm his teacher. So what?!
Just hold on a second!
It's not like we HAVE to kill him!
ちょっと待ってくれ！
なにも殺すことはないだろう？
Shouldn't we be thinking of some
other way to get through this?
ほかに方法があるかどうか
考えるべきなんじゃないか？
（佳乃）その方法が間違ってたら？
And if that other way is wrong?!
What if no one survives because of it?!
そのせいで
誰も生き残れないとしたら？
Are you listening to yourself?!
（古田）あんた 何言ってるんだ！
If you don't want to shoot, you can stay here.
撃ちたくなければ
ここに残ってください
我々だけで やりますから
（野崎）ああ？
We'll take care of it.
Hey!
（古田）おい！
Hey, wait! Hey!
（古田）おい 待て！ おい！
Look what you've done, Gantz.
やってくれるぜ ガンツ
But I won't lose...
負けるかよ
I won't lose!
負けるかよ！
Cosplay
Paradise
Kurono!
（梶浦）玄野！ お前には
何の恨みもないが生き残るためだ！
I have nothing against you,
but my life is at stake!
Please understand that!
分かってくれ！
（古田）やめなさい！
Don't do this!
（室戸）今更 話し合いなんて…
It's too late to start trying to talk things over.
（梶浦・室戸）ウワッ！
（みかの悲鳴）
（割れる音）
（古田）隠れて！ 隠れて！
Take cover! Take cover!
Kurono! Don't do this!
玄野君 やめたまえ！
（室戸）くそ…
Son of a bitch...
Eat this!
（計）この！
Hey! Take cover!
おい 隠れろ
You're not running the show, hotshot!
（計）
偉そうに先導してんじゃねえ！
てめえらが
いちばんワルだろうが！
You're the evilest ones here!
（殴る音）
ウワッ！ ウッ…
（室戸）アア… 助けて 殺されるよ
Help! He's going to kill me...
Kurono! Stop it!
（佳乃）玄野君 やめなさい！
Teacher...
先生…
If you make one more move, I'll shoot.
１歩でも動いたら… 先生 撃つわよ
What are you doing? Put the gun down!
何をしてる？ 銃を下ろせ！
Kurono, come over here now!
（佳乃）
こっちに来なさい 玄野君！
（梶浦）ハァ ハァ ハァ…
What are you doing? Teacher...
何だよ？ 先生
No one wants to believe they're dead.
誰だって 自分が死んだなんて
思いたくないのよ
もし あなたを殺せば
生き残れるっていうんなら―
If someone says I can live by killing you,
then I... I...
私は… 私は…
You'd... shoot me?
俺を撃つっていうのかよ？ 先生！
Teacher!
What else am I supposed to do?!
（佳乃）
ほかに どうしろっていうのよ？
Hey, teacher, that's enough.
I'll take it from here.
（梶浦）先生 もういいですよ
あとは俺が やりますから
But...
（佳乃）で… でも…
Just get back!
下がっててください 先生！
Kurono, are you still willing to fight?
玄野君 これでも まだ戦うかよ？
You're taking her hostage?
（斉藤）人質ってことですか
Mr. Kajiura, what do you think you're doing?!
（古田）梶浦さん 何してるんだ？
彼女は関係ないだろう 離せ！
She has nothing to do with this! Let her go!
You know I can't do that!
We still have to kill the Kurono Alien!
そうはいかないんじゃないですか？
我々は玄野星人を
倒さなきゃならないんですよ
I have to do this.
この際 しょうがない
玄野君 どうする？
Kurono! What are you going to do?
君が いつまでも抵抗してると
彼女が傷つくぞ！
If you continue to resist,
I'm going to have to hurt her!
Are you okay with that?
それでも いいのか？
Idiot. Can't he think of any other way?
（室戸）
バ～カ ほかに方法ねえのかよ？
This is for your own good. Stop fighting back!
悪いことは言わない
これ以上 抵抗するな！
If you do, no harm will come to her!
そうすれば 彼女に危害は加えない
Bastards!
あいつら…
（みか）玄野君…
Kurono...
Stop pushing us around!
（梶浦）
これ以上 みんなを追い詰めるな
Stop pushing us around!
Everyone wants to survive!
誰だって生き残りたいんだよ
Right?
でしょう？ フフッ…
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
（佳乃）
人生は所詮 迷宮みたいなものよ
Life is like a labyrinth:
Once you get lost, it's not easy
to find the way out.
一度迷ったら
出口は そう簡単に見えないから
Oh well. It doesn't matter anymore.
まあ 別にいいけどね
Next episode,
次回
“出られない迷宮はないんだ”
"No Labyrinth Is Inescapable"